affiliatemarketingdude.com 2019-07-15

# Make Money Online - Affiliate Marketing - Business Opportunity

**** **** **

****SimpleSitesbigProfits.com PRIVACY POLICY****

**Welcome to SimpleSitesbigProfits.com website. We respect your privacy.   This statement informs you as to how we collect, safeguard and use information you provide us. We want you to feel comfortable using our website and services and encourage you to read this Privacy Policy, detailing the online practices for SimpleSitesbigProfits.com (“Marcs"). **

****Marcs Services:****

**On SimpleSitesbigProfits.com you can download software and content, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, or participate in online forums or communities. In exchange for Marcs content or services the user may decide download software, share personal information or view upfront advertising; it is up to the user. A variety of products and services are available at Marcs and Marcs may collect different types and levels of personal information for each model, product or service.**

****The Information We Collect** **

**The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.**

**There are also times when you can submit information about other people. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.**

**We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider.**

****How We Use the Information** **

**We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.**

**We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or to fulfill a request by you or to contact you about your account with us.**

**We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your referrals. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.**

**If you choose to submit content for publication we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.**

**The information we collect in connection with our online communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.**

**We sometimes use non-personally identifiable information to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.**

**We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.**

**Agents and contractors of SimpleSitesbigProfits.com who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for SimpleSitesbigProfits.com.**

****Informed Consent** **

**SimpleSitesbigProfits.com will not disclose personally identifiable information to companies not owned by us who want to market products or services to you without your prior informed consent.**

****Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors** **

**SimpleSitesbigProfits.com contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by websites that are not our own.**

**From time to time SimpleSitesbigProfits.com may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions or deals that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit. After such submissions, SimpleSitesbigProfits.com has no control over third-party sponsors' use of this information.**

**SimpleSitesbigProfits.com will provide notice if third-party sponsors will so obtain such information. SimpleSitesbigProfits.com may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information by such third parties or the methods by which third-parties collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs).**

****Third-party Ad Serving** **

**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to SimpleSitesbigProfits.com in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the SimpleSitesbigProfits.com website, our third-party advertising companies may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.**

****Cookies** **

**To enhance your experience with our site, our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our websites. However, once you choose to furnish SimpleSitesbigProfits.com with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings at SimpleSitesbigProfits.com, to save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" may be used to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy.**

****Our Commitment to Security** **

**We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online, but cannot protect against third party criminal acts.**

****Special Note for Parents** **

**In an effort to be compliant with the Children's Online Protection Privacy Act (COPPA) it is our policy to collect no personally identifiable information from children. Therefore, all individuals are required to over the age of 13 years to submit any personal information.**

****How to Contact Us** **

**If you have any questions or concerns about this SimpleSitesbigProfits.com Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via email at the following address:**

**SimpleSitesbigProfits.com  
607 Elmira Rd PMB 265  
Vacaville, Ca 95687**

**_Marcus Campbell_ _\- Internet Marketing Specialist  
Contact Info: Direct Office Line - 800-893-0675 | 9-5PST M-F | Vacaville, California_**

` [ ](http://www.onlinebusinessbureau.com/Companyrating.cfm?Company_ID=1834965http://www.onlinebusinessbureau.com/Companyrating.cfm?Company_ID=1834965)`

To the best of my knowledge the information contained in this book and videos is true and accurate.  We cannot guarantee that you will make money using these principals.  Please use discretion when marketing online and contact a lawyer for any legal advice.  We are not responsible for how you decide to use this information.

**

** This is a guide showing you how I have used the simple sites big profits method to generate an income online.  I cannot guarantee that you will make money following these steps. it is possible you may even loose money.**
